

# DANIEL DOMINGUEZ SOFTWARE PRODUCT MANAGER

# Project Manager / Certified ScrumMaster®

September 26, 1982 35 years old Colombian, Single



K 49 No 91-86 AP 402 Bogotá, COLOMBIA



(+57) 319-219-4399 (+57 1) 675-1189



dominguezdaniel@live.com



dominguezdaniel



dominguezdaniel



@dominguezdaniel



dominguezdaniel



http://x.co/idaniel

# SUMMARY

Engineer with studies from Colombia, France and Canada. Over 8 years of experience working on Internet-related products and services companies in Colombia and USA. With major expertise on Agile Methodologies, Project Management, Product Development, Digital Marketing and Entrepreneurship.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Product Owner, Webpy webpy.co

Colombia/USA — Jan 2017 - September 2017

Product planning, ideation and release under design thinking and lean methodologies.

#### Scrum Master, Torre Technologies torre.co

Colombia/USA - Dec 2014 - Dec 2016

Certified ScrumMaster®. Agile scrum development framework for managing product.

# Project Manager, DLD Agencia Digital dld.com.co

Colombia/USA - Apr 2014 - Nov 2014

Planning and execution on Google engagement and web app implementations.

#### Project Manager, VML vml.com

Colombia/USA — Oct 2013 - Mar 2013

Planning, execution and closing projects for Boehringer Ingelheim, Merck and MediaFiche.

#### Online Marketing Manager, .CO Internet go.co

Colombia/USA — Aug 2012 - May 2013

Tracking and evaluation of marketing initiatives for .CO domains.

#### Co-Founder, I-Azul i-azul.com

Colombia/USA — Jan 2009 - Jul 2012

Consulting, strategy and development in E-Business, E-Commerce and E-Marketing.

# **EDUCATION**

# University of Alberta (Canada)

Specialization, Software Product Management — 2015-2016

# Université Pierre et Marie Curie (France)

Master's Degree, Engineering Science — 2008-2008

# Université des Sciences et Technologies de Lille (France)

Professional Master, Automation - 2006-2007

# Universidad Militar Nueva Granada (Colombia)

Engineer, Mechatronics — 2000-2005

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish (Native), English (Full Proficiency), French (Full Proficiency)

# **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, GIT, VPL, SQL, Web Design, Scrum, Project Management, Agile, Team Management, Communication, Leadership, Planning, Documentation, Atlassian Suite, Online Marketing, Google Analytics, Google Adwords, Microsoft Azure, Wix Developer.

#### **INTERESTS**

Robots, Arduino, Programming, Gig Economy, Reading, Traveling, Top Eleven, Zen.

#### **REFERENCES**

**Omar Duque**, Director of Engineering at Huge (+57) 300-386-7557 - Colombia **Lorena Dominguez**, Sister, UI/UX Specialist (+1) 437-983-8050 - Canada